Office of Student Services, School of Dental Medicine Records UA235
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Post Graduate files, 1948 -- 2018; UA235.002; 42.5 Linear Feet
  - Qari, Maha R. Perio/MS 2010, 2013; UA235.002.074.00010 (Box 74)
  - Quinta, Anthony Perio 2010, 2013; UA235.002.074.00011 (Box 74)
  - Reti, Robert OMS 2009, 2013; UA235.002.074.00012 (Box 74)
  - Reynolds, Renee C. Ortho 2011, 2013; UA235.002.074.00013 (Box 74)
  - Saunders, Eileen M. Pedo 2011, 2013; UA235.002.074.00014 (Box 74)
  - Shannon, Patrick Perio 2010, 2013; UA235.002.074.00015 (Box 74)
  - Shepherd, Holly Prostho 2010, 2013; UA235.002.074.00016 (Box 74)
  - Tachasirinugune, Sunida Est 2012, 2013; UA235.002.074.00017 (Box 74)
  - Tamasas, Basma CMD 2012, 2013; UA235.002.074.00018 (Box 74)
  - Tamasas, Basma I. MS 2011, 2013; UA235.002.074.00019 (Box 74)
  - Tolani, Hitesh GPR 2012, 2013; UA235.002.074.00020 (Box 74)
  - Wadsworth, Kurtis L. Endo 2011, 2013; UA235.002.074.00021 (Box 74)
  - Weisner, Michael Perio 2010, 2013; UA235.002.074.00022 (Box 74)
  - Wiseman, Kevin C. Ortho 2011, 2013; UA235.002.074.00023 (Box 74)
  - Wu, Xueying Implant 2012, 2013; UA235.002.074.00024 (Box 74)
  - Yoon, Jongwon Prostho 2010, 2013; UA235.002.074.00025 (Box 74)
  - Zee, Robert Pedo 2011, 2013; UA235.002.074.00026 (Box 74)
  - Alakkad, Tarik, 2018; UA235.005307; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 13)
    Esthetics
  - Aldakhil, Haifa, 2018; UA235.005308; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 14)
    Pediatrics
  - Abdelsalam, Nairouz, 2018; UA235.005309; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - Alakkad, Layali, 2018; UA235.005310; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - Alghamdi, Mansour, 2018; UA235.005311; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 17)
    Prosthodontics
  - Alkadhi, Ruba, 2018; UA235.005312; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 18)
    Dental Sleep
  - Alshawaf, Bahaa, 2018; UA235.005313; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 19)
    Advanced Digital Prosthodontic and Implant Dentistry (ADPI)
  - Alulaiyan, Mohammed, 2018; UA235.005314; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 20)
  - Almoharib, Hani, 2018; UA235.005315; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 21)
    Periodontology
  - Alvarez-Novoa, Marta, 2018; UA235.005316; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 22)
  - Alwael, Abiar, 2018; UA235.005317; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 23)
  - Ayoub, Solafa, 2018; UA235.005318; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 24)
  - Babarinde, Adeduntan, 2018; UA235.005319; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 25)
    Orthodontics
  - Barashi, Mohammed, 2018; UA235.005320; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 26)
  - Bugshan, Amr, 2018; UA235.005321; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 27)
    OralMedicine
  - Bui, Quynh, 2018; UA235.005322; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 28)
  - Chen, Yo-wei, 2018; UA235.005323; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 29)
  - Bensreti, Husam, 2018; UA235.005324; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 30)
    MS
  - Chou, Tina, 2018; UA235.005325; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 31)
    Endodontics
  - Dardeer, Faisal, 2018; UA235.005326; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 32)
  - Elias, Hiam (Amy), 2018; UA235.005327; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 33)
  - English, Ray III, 2018; UA235.005328; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 34)
    OralSurgery
  - Fahey, Ross, 2018; UA235.005329; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 35)
  - Fontaine, Alyssa, 2018; UA235.005330; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 36)
    AEGD
  - Fung, Katharina, 2016; UA235.005331; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 37)
    ORTHO
  - Gallant, Lauren, 2018; UA235.005332; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 38)
  - Gill, Gina, 2016; UA235.005333; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 39)
  - Guerra Percolla, Julissa, 2018; UA235.005334; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 40)
  - Hatzipetrou, Kristina, 2018; UA235.005335; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 41)
  - Heck, Hanna, 2018; UA235.005336; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 42)
  - Hoina, Adam, 2016; UA235.005337; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 43)
  - Kalthoum, Zaina, 2018; UA235.005338; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 44)
  - Koleini, Pardis, 2018; UA235.005339; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 45)
  - Konrad, Danielle, 2018; UA235.005340; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 46)
    GPR
  - Kuo, Alan, 2018; UA235.005341; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 47)
  - Lee, Janice, 2016; UA235.005342; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 48)
  - Lei, Kai Chyuan, 2018; UA235.005343; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 49)
  - Marzouca, Lauren, 2018; UA235.005344; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - McClure, Alexander, 2018; UA235.005345; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Min, Sun, 2018; UA235.005346; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Moini, Morvarid, 2018; UA235.005347; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Nassief, Sarah, 2018; UA235.005348; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Penn, Christina, 2018; UA235.005349; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Qu, Wenyu, 2018; UA235.005350; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Ramirez Martinez, Fabiola, 2018; UA235.005351; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Rapti, Martha, 2018; UA235.005352; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Refahi, Pooyan, 2018; UA235.005353; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Bozarth, Seth, 2016; UA235.005354; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Sasthri-Rajaputrage, Sajini, 2018; UA235.005355; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Shamirian, Paul, 2018; UA235.005356; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Smith, Darren, 2018; UA235.005357; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Tae, Il Ho, 2018; UA235.005358; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - Tagerman, Samantha, 2018; UA235.005359; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - Toopchi, Shabnam, 2018; UA235.005360; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 17)
  - Tran, Wendy, 2018; UA235.005361; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - Treff, Sarah, 2018; UA235.005362; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 19)
  - Tyler, Kyle, 2018; UA235.005363; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 20)
    OMFS intern
  - Wolfe, Anya, 2018; UA235.005364; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 21)
  - Wong, Alex, 2018; UA235.005365; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 22)
  - Wu, Stephanie, 2018; UA235.005366; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 23)
  - Ye, Stanley, 2018; UA235.005367; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 24)
  - Abdullah, Abeer, 2018; UA235.005368; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 25)
  - Abdulmajeed, Afnan, 2018; UA235.005369; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 26)
  - Alamer, Nora, 2017; UA235.005370; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 27)
  - Alaqel, Salem, 2016; UA235.005371; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 28)
  - Alenezi, Hamed, 2017; UA235.005372; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 29)
  - Alghanim, Manar, 2016; UA235.005373; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 30)
  - Alhazmi, Nora, 2016; UA235.005374; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 31)
  - Alhazmi, Hesham, 2016; UA235.005375; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 32)
  - Alkadhi, Ruba, 2016; UA235.005376; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 33)
  - Almershed, Sarah, 2017; UA235.005377; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 34)
  - Almershed, Sarah, 2013; UA235.005378; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 35)
  - Baflah, Lamia, 2017; UA235.005379; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 36)
  - Baflah, Lamia, 2014; UA235.005380; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 37)
    CMD
  - Barton, Jennifer, 2017; UA235.005381; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 38)
  - Gascoyne, Joshua, 2017; UA235.005382; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 39)
  - Geary, Sean, 2017; UA235.005383; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 40)
  - Gold, Jessica, 2017; UA235.005384; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 41)
  - Harp, Fernando, 2017; UA235.005385; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 42)
  - Hegazi, Fahad, 2017; UA235.005386; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 43)
  - Hegazi, Fahad, 2017; UA235.005387; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 44)
  - Isaiah, Federica, 2017; UA235.005388; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 45)
  - Jabr, Yazan, 2017; UA235.005389; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 46)
  - Johnson, Scott, 2017; UA235.005390; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 47)
  - Khanbodaghi, Azita, 2017; UA235.005391; 1 Folder(s) (Box 104, Folder 48)
  - Khayat, Waad, 2011; UA235.005392; 1 Folder(s) (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Khayat, Waad, 2016; UA235.005393; 1 Folder(s) (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Leung, Derek, 2017; UA235.005394; 1 Folder(s) (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Lin, Christopher, 2017; UA235.005395; 1 Folder(s) (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Mansouri, Noor, 2017; UA235.005396; 1 Folder(s) (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Marcuschamer, Eduardo, 2009; UA235.005397; 1 Folder(s) (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Kreitzer, Michael, 2017; UA235.005398; 1 Folder(s) (Box 105, Folder 7)
- Grade sheets, 1966 -- 2004; UA235.003; 2.4 Linear Feet
  This series contains course grade reports for doctor of dental medicine students and grade changes for courses. It also contains certificate information describing how student names should appear on their Certificate of Achievement.
  This series is arranged as found, loosely chronologically.
  - Grade Report, 1990; UA235.003.039.00001 (Box 39)
  - Grade Report International Students, 1990; UA235.003.039.00002 (Box 39)
  - Grade Report, 1991; UA235.003.039.00003 (Box 39)
  - Grade Report International Students, 1991; UA235.003.039.00004 (Box 39)
  - Grade Report, 1992; UA235.003.039.00005 (Box 39)
  - Grade Report International Students, 1992; UA235.003.039.00006 (Box 39)
  - Grade Report, 1993; UA235.003.039.00007 (Box 39)
  - Grade Report International Students, 1994; UA235.003.039.00008 (Box 39)
  - Grade Report International Students, 1995; UA235.003.039.00009 (Box 39)
  - Grade Report, 1997; UA235.003.039.00010 (Box 39)
  - Grade Report, 1998; UA235.003.039.00011 (Box 39)
  - Grade Report, 1999; UA235.003.039.00012 (Box 39)
  - Grade Report International Students Commencement, 1999; UA235.003.039.00013 (Box 39)
  - Grades before, 1966 -- 1967; UA235.003.039.00014 (Box 39)
  - Grades P. G., 1971 -- 1972; UA235.003.039.00015 (Box 39)
  - Grades in Advanced Education, 1979 -- 1980; UA235.003.039.00016 (Box 39)
  - Advanced Education Grades, 1980 -- 1981; UA235.003.039.00017 (Box 39)
  - Advanced Education Grades, 1981 -- 1982; UA235.003.039.00018 (Box 39)
  - Advanced Education Grades, 1982 -- 1983; UA235.003.039.00019 (Box 39)
  - Advanced Education Grades, 1983 -- 1984; UA235.003.039.00020 (Box 39)
  - Advanced Education Grades, 1984 -- 1985; UA235.003.039.00021 (Box 39)
  - Grade Report, 1985 -- 1986; UA235.003.039.00022 (Box 39)
  - Grade Report, 1986 -- 1987; UA235.003.039.00023 (Box 39)
  - Grade Report, 1987 -- 1988; UA235.003.039.00024 (Box 39)
  - Grade Report, 1988 -- 1989; UA235.003.039.00025 (Box 39)
  - Grade Report, 1990 -- 1991; UA235.003.039.00026 (Box 39)
  - Grade Report, 1991 -- 1992; UA235.003.040.00001 (Box 40)
  - Grade Report, 1996 -- 1997; UA235.003.040.00002 (Box 40)
  - Grade Report, 1989 -- 1990; UA235.003.040.00003 (Box 40)
  - Certificates, 1999; UA235.003.040.00004 (Box 40)
  - Certificates, 1998; UA235.003.040.00005 (Box 40)
  - Certificates, 1996; UA235.003.040.00006 (Box 40)
  - Certificates, 1995; UA235.003.040.00007 (Box 40)
  - Certificates, 1994; UA235.003.040.00008 (Box 40)
  - Certificates, 1993; UA235.003.040.00009 (Box 40)
  - Certificates, 1992; UA235.003.040.00010 (Box 40)
  - Certificates, 1991; UA235.003.040.00011 (Box 40)
  - Certificates, 1990; UA235.003.040.00012 (Box 40)
  - Certificates, 1989; UA235.003.040.00013 (Box 40)
  - Certificates, 1988; UA235.003.040.00014 (Box 40)
  - Certificates, 1987; UA235.003.040.00015 (Box 40)
  - Certificates, 1986; UA235.003.040.00016 (Box 40)
  - Certificates, 1985; UA235.003.040.00017 (Box 40)
  - Certificates, 1984; UA235.003.040.00018 (Box 40)
  - Certificates, 1983; UA235.003.040.00019 (Box 40)
  - Certificates, 1982; UA235.003.040.00020 (Box 40)
  - Certificates, 1981; UA235.003.040.00021 (Box 40)
  - Grade Sheets, 2000; UA235.003.040.00022 (Box 40)
  - Grade Sheets, 2000; UA235.003.040.00023 (Box 40)
  - Grade Sheets / Int'l Grade Sheets, 2002; UA235.003.040.00024 (Box 40)
  - Grade Sheets / Int'l Grade Sheets, 2002; UA235.003.040.00025 (Box 40)
  - Grade Sheets, 2003; UA235.003.040.00026 (Box 40)
  - Int'l Grade Sheets, 2003; UA235.003.040.00027 (Box 40)
  - Int'l Grade Sheets, 2004; UA235.003.040.00028 (Box 40)
- Withdrawn or Dismissed students, 1966 -- 2008; UA235.004; 8.4 Linear Feet
  This series contains primarily doctor of dental medicine student folders of students who withdrew or were dismissed from the School of Dental Medicine. Types of records found within student files include transcripts of Dental School and undergraduate institutions, admission letters and recommendations, applications, evaluations, photographs, and other personal information. The year listed for each student is the date of their graduation.
- 2016 accessions, 1991 -- 2015; UA235.005; 12 Linear Feet 10 record cartons
  This series is arranged in rough alphabetical order.
  Records containing information related to student education, staff and faculty employment, and Board of Trustees records are closed for 75 years from the date of creation.
  This series contains student files for 2015 graduates and postgraduates, 2008 postgraduate clearance forms, 1991-1992 transfer student files, 2011-2015 GPR files, and files for discontinued and dismissed students.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Transferred by the Office of Student Services, School of Dental Medicine, 2016, accession UA-2017-023.
  - D'15 Graduates A-Ch, 1991 -- 2015; UA235.005.080 (Box 80)
  - D'15 Graduates Ch-I, 1991 -- 2015; UA235.005.081; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 81)
  - D'15 Graduates J-M, 1991 -- 2015; UA235.005.082; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 82)
  - D'15 Graduates N-Sa, 1991 -- 2015; UA235.005.083; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 83)
  - D'15 Graduates Sc-Z, 1991 -- 2015; UA235.005.084; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 84)
  - Discontinued Students A-Z, 1991 -- 2015; UA235.005.085; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 85)
  - Discontinued Students Misc.; Postgraduates A, 1991 -- 2015; UA235.005.086; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 86)
  - Postgraduates B-P, 1991 -- 2015; UA235.005.087; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 87)
  - Postgraduates P-Z; Dismissed Students; Postgraduate Clearance Forms; Transfer Student Files, 1991 -- 2015; UA235.005.088; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 88)
  - GPR Files, 1991 -- 2015; UA235.005.089; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 89)
- Additional accessions, UA235.005097
  - D'14 J. Abraham-V. Dmytrvk, 2014; UA235-001 (Box 1)
  - D'14 K. Dunmire-L. Lam, 2014; UA235-002 (Box 2)
  - D'14 J. Lapierre-R. Patel, 2014; UA235-003 (Box 3)
  - D'14 S.Paul-W. Wang, 2014; UA235-004 (Box 4)
  - D'14 M. Webb-PG'14 D. Malouf, 2014; UA235-005 (Box 5)
  - PG'14 J. Manolakis-J. Young, 2014; UA235-006 (Box 6)